

Franco Stassen

Personal

Franco Stassen Name

Address Pretoria

Phone number 082 343 9971

Email franco.stassen75@gmail.com

Date of birth 04-07-2001

Gender Male

Website www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-stassen-6806951b0

Resume objective

I am a junior IT professional with a passion for data handling. I find it fascinating to explore data, derive insights, and communicate those insights effectively. Most of my day consists of SQL scripting, which helps me work efficiently with data to develop insights and solve problems. I also have hands on experience with Microsoft SSRS and Power BI, which I use to create meaningful reports and visualizations that support informed decision-making.

Education and Qualifications

Matric Certificate Hoerskool Montana, Pretoria	2015 - 2019
IT Systems Development CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2021 - 2021
Microsoft MTA: Introduction to programming using Python CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2021
Microsoft MTA: Introduction to programming using HTML and CSS CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2021
Microsoft MTA: Introduction to programming using JavaScript CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2021
Software Development CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2022
Database Development CTU Training Solutions, Pretoria	2023



Work experience

Junior Software Developer and Syspro Consultant

Jan 2024 - Present

Lancea Konsult, Pretoria

Sound Engineer

Kilowatt Productions, Pretoria

Oct 2021 - Present

DJ for events including wedding and artist music shows. Side hustle on weekends.



Gym, Gaming

References

KevinKilowatt0825247885Productions

CTU Training

Solutions

info@kilowattproductions.co.za

Alesia De Beer
0861100395
alesiadb@ctutraining.co.za

Languages

- English
- Afrikaans